My Little Pony: Equestria Girls - Spring Breakdown is a action,
adventure, comedy film directed by Ishi Rudell.
The Equestria Girls spend their spring break on a yacht.
It's Spring Break and the Mane 7 are about to board the most
glorious yacht ever for a relaxing cruise.
But Rainbow Dash is convinced that Equestrian Magic is on the
loose and won't let anyone rest until she finds it.
Rainbow Dash / Applejack (voice), played by Ashleigh Ball.
Pinkie Pie / Fluttershy (voice), played by Andrea Libman.
Twilight Sparkle / Princess Twilight Sparkle (voice), played by Tara Strong.
Sunset Shimmer / Twilight Sparkle (singing voice), played by Rebecca Shoichet.
Rarity (voice), played by Tabitha St. Germain.
Spike (voice), played by Cathy Weseluck.
My Little Pony: Equestria Girls – Spring Breakdown is a 2019 animated television special within Hasbro's My Little
Pony: Equestria Girls franchise, itself a spin-off of the 2010 relaunch of the My Little Pony toy line.
The special was directed by Ishi Rudell and Katrina Hadley, written and edited by Nick
Confalone, and produced by DHX Media Vancouver for Hasbro Studios in the United States.
Premiered on Discovery Family (a joint venture between Discovery, Inc.
and Hasbro) on March 30, 2019, it is the third one-hour Equestria Girls special, following Forgotten Friendship and Rollercoaster of Friendship
(both 2018), and preceding Sunset's Backstage Pass and Holidays Unwrapped (released later in July and November, respectively).
The tone is lighthearted.